Bye bye!
Great!
Desert fox
I will try my best to diy!
schemo ana
Yes, yes, yes...
new
It will never end.
But, um, Yuna is a person who will die, so I will go slowly and surely.
Yes, slowly. Seriously, slowly. Slower than you think.
I'll go at a speed I enjoy.
I hate red lights the most.
I really underestimated it. I didn't think it would be so hard.
Also, I realized that I love the members.
You always have the members around you at gigs and stuff,
I still can't do it alone, I can't do it alone, I thought.
When I ran the marathon today by myself.
Good job.
Have you changed?
It's not about bonding anymore.
Not bonding and shit. Not that kind of shit.
Thank you so much. Seriously, thank you.
But if you run once in practice and sustain it for a while, your legs will get used to it,
It makes it easier to run. I learned that my legs will be heavier, but it will be easier to run.
Yay!
I did it!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
You are so happy, aren't you?
They are all so dependable,
It's like they make me feel like I'm dependable, too,
They are all really wonderful kids,
I want to do my best to catch up with them.
So, I will pass the baton to Takae-kun.
I will really do my best this time, too.
I'm in a bit of trouble.It's a bit of a mess.
It's like we're finally at the end of the line.
We have three more to go.
We have about 2.5 more to go.
Yuna is at the halfway point, too.
It's not good.
But I can see Tokyo Tower on the way,
I'll be at the halfway point when I get to the end of Tokyo Tower,
I'd like to run while feeling the Tokyo cityscape.
I'm so nervous.
It's 6:34.
That's early.
Oh no.
It's running!
Great!
That's a good pace!
He's got time.
I can do it! I can do it!
You're doing great!
No problem at all.
Good job!
Tired!
It's so hard!
Untertitelung
Oh, yeah!
It hasn't stopped for a long time.
That's great, you did it!
You did it. I thought it was great.
Oh, that's great.
I thought so.
Anyway, count your cossacks.
Keep up the pace.
Never stop.
I was thinking
But then I saw Yuya climbing up the mountain.But something about Yuya's climbing.
It's been going on for a long time.
It's a tough climb, isn't it?
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
Go, go, go, go!
You can do it!
Oh, my God!
Yeah!
Go for it!
I'd rather...
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
I've been running thinking I'm going to retire.
It's tougher to retire, isn't it?
For everyone who always supports Yanagida,
Today was also a way to return the favor,
I want to do my best to finish the race,
I want to run as hard as I can to finish the race.
Yanagida will be back.
And the next winner is Kouen-kun.
Bye bye.
500 to go.
Okay, with 100 to go.
Gachiro.
Gachiro?
Gachi-cha-cha
Oh, big one.
Oh, here it comes.
Here it comes.
Hang on, hang on.
On the edge! On the edge! On the edge!
Run!
On the edge! On the edge!
I can go, I can go, I can go!
One hundred! I'm on it!
Fast!Fast!
Go, go, go, go!
Thank you!
Come on! Come on!
I got it.
I got it!
Let's go!
I'm going to run!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Follow me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's good.
It's okay.
Thank you for your time.
Nothing's stopped?
Great!
That's really great!
You did great!
That's too much!
I'm not walking!
That's great!
It's so hot!
Good job!
It's hot! It's hot!
Oh, man, I'm so nervous. Oh, man!
I got it!
This last one's on the scan!
Oh, no!
It's on the scan!
Don't go overboard!
I don't have the energy!
No, no, no, I'm fine!
We're not going to make it to the show!Seriously, the show is bad!
Everyone's hot, so don't worry!
I'm fine!
I'm really okay!
I'm really determined!
I mean, Haruma, I went to the show!
You can go! Good luck! I was so excited! I'm so excited!
That's great!
You're gonna do it, Haruma!
Haruma, I'll do it!
He told me I was just using Yuna Yajima's simplicity for my own good!
It's Celtia's! Celtier's!
The pace is really fast now!
Isn't this going to be like a relay race? Are you sure about this?
Is this a relay race?
I'm winding it up! Follow me!
I'll follow you!
Everyone has been telling their own stories and running through the race.
Let's take that good flow and give it to the last leader.
I hope we can take that good flow and pass it on to the last leader!
Oh man, I'm so glad I'm getting in on this.
Yeah!
Go for it!
Oh!
Yeah!
Hurry up, huh?
Quick, huh?
Quick!
That was fast!
That was awesome!
That's so cool!
That was awesome! It's so cool!
Ah! I can't believe it!Ah! Fly!
Fly!
Oh!
Yeah!
Nice, nice, nice!
You're still at 5 kilos, right?
Can you do it? Can you go?
Ready?
Too soon!
I'm gonna die.
I'll die like a normal person.
Oh, that's hard, isn't it?
I'm gonna die fast.
That's amazing.
I'm gonna go now.
Good job, good job! Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Quick!
Yes, Koi-kun, I'll go anywhere!
Five kilometers to go.
Let's go as fast as we can!
I think this is a milestone for all of us, and I hope we can all pass on what we've built together in good condition until the end.
I think there are bonds that can be formed, so I think it's a great challenge.
Running through something that is a bit important means that we were able to receive everyone's thoughts and feelings and connect with them.
I think it will probably be a hot one.
What do you want to give to Mr. Sasaki? Baton
I was a little nervous, so I told him that I'm not nervous anymore.
I want to run as fast as I can to let him know that it's okay to run as usual.
It's important!
It's the last race!
You can do it!
Aria can do it!
Come on!
I'll do my best!
Come on!Good luck!
Hang in there Ali!
I didn't really feel it this morning, I was saying it's in 12 hours...
I just woke up and I'm already the most nervous I've ever been!
I'm so nervous!
I'm going to do my best to finish the race, and I'll do my best to carry everyone's thoughts with me.
I'm going to carry everyone's thoughts and feelings on my shoulders and do my best with all my guts!
Phew!
I'm off!
I'll see you there!
I'll definitely, definitely impress you with my guts!
I'll do my best.
I'll definitely impress you with my perseverance
I'll carry everyone's hard work on my back.
I'm hoping that the cooler nighttime temperatures will help us finish on time.
I'm hoping to finish the race in time, but most of all, I'm going to do my best to finish the race.
I will do my best with my guts, carrying everyone's thoughts and feelings on my back.
Don't slip up!
What's that?
Wow.
Go, go, go!
You'll get a compliment at this point!
I'll do my best!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Are you cold? Cold?
I'm fine.
Rain okay?
How many kilometers are we?
Five kilometers.
I think we've got about six more kilometers to go.
95.96 kilometers.
Six more kilometers.
I'll do my best.
You want to go again?You want to go again?
I'm ready.
Wow, Anri, you're early.
Good luck, Mani!
Let's go to the winter one tomorrow.
Good luck!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I'll do my best when I know you're all here.
We're like a family.
We're like a second family.
Through this relay race, we can help each other more.
and the bond of cooperation among us
I'll carry that on my back to the end.
I hope I can carry that on my shoulders
I hope that I will be able to carry that on my shoulders at the end.
3,2,1, start!
Lovely
I'm going all out
I'm going to launch it
Every time you are frustrating
I can see it now
This voice keeps on going Good dance
It was a love that will never happen again
New moon is forever
is funny
I'm so sorry
Help me
I felt like we weren't friends...
right?
From one side
Like a fuse.
Here we go!
Come on!
Come on... My brother Asasaki...
My brother Asa-saki...I'm going to go flying in.
I'm going to fly in and out.
Here you go.
Wow!
Look at this!
Yes!
Wow.
Three, two, one.
Ooh.
Yay!
I love it.
Yay.
Yay! Yay!
Congratulations.
It's hard work.
You worked so hard.
I think I can get through anything.
Ew.
Hang in there, hang in there.
Good luck!
Oh, I can already picture everyone's face
I'm not alone.
I'm not alone
I felt really strong inside.
I feel stronger, so from now on
I'm going to think of everyone.
I'd like to think of everyone
I'd like to get over it.
I mean, I wouldn't be here if it weren't for you guys.
Wow!
I love you guys!
100km night was a great success!100km night was a great success!
Yay! - Yay!
Yay!
Let's all go to Tokyo Dome!
Let's go!
Yay!
Wait for me!